<geeklist id="58160" termsofuse="http://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse">
<postdate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 18:21:12 +0000</postdate>
<postdate_timestamp>1282846872</postdate_timestamp>
<editdate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 18:03:51 +0000</editdate>
<editdate_timestamp>1282845831</editdate_timestamp>
<thumbs>37</thumbs>

<username>Quarashi</username> 
<title>The television series you are currently watching</title>
<description>Based on my geeklist: [geeklist=58125][/geeklist]. I thought I would post a geeklist about television and see if this garners more responses than reading does. With that said...

The title pretty much speaks for itself. Post the television series you are currently watching now. How do you like it so far? What do you plan on watching next? Have you watched anything decent lately? </description>

	<comment username="Iorekbyrnison" date="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 06:56:25 +0000" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 06:56:25 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 06:56:25 +0000" thumbs="3">
I don't watch much television, but friends had recommended "Dexter" so I gave it a try and blech.  Just awful.  I don't get the hype, and I usually love that kind of thing.  I did buy the first season of the British show "Hex", though, (on sale at Wal-Mart!!) and really enjoyed that.  
</comment>
<comment username="Wind Lane" date="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 09:11:47 +0000" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 09:11:47 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 09:11:47 +0000" thumbs="4">
Nobody's watching Bones or Mythbusters or The Soup or American Chopper or Word Girl (a PBS cartoon that's actually pretty darn good...it's weird) or Robot Chicken or Venture Brothers?

I'd have thought there would be more than just good sci/fi, top notch drama, and prime time cartoons on this list.
</comment>
<comment username="J.L.Robert" date="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 17:04:17 +0000" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 17:04:17 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 17:04:17 +0000" thumbs="3">
[q="Wind Lane"]Nobody's watching Bones or Mythbusters or The Soup or American Chopper or Word Girl (a PBS cartoon that's actually pretty darn good...it's weird) or Robot Chicken or Venture Brothers?

I'd have thought there would be more than just good sci/fi, top notch drama, and prime time cartoons on this list.[/q]

I just got to this list...
</comment>
<comment username="OrangeCat X" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 17:07:58 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 17:07:58 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 17:07:58 +0000" thumbs="4">
[q="Wind Lane"]Nobody's watching Bones or Mythbusters or The Soup or American Chopper or Word Girl (a PBS cartoon that's actually pretty darn good...it's weird) or Robot Chicken or Venture Brothers?[/q]Mythbusters, Robot Chicken and Venture Brothers. 

I stood in line for 2 hours at comic-con, trying to get into the Venture Brother's panel. 

This series is one of the media that is responsible for revitalizing my interest in running RPGs; Both Fantasy and Superhero. You can be [b]an awesome killing machine[/b], and [b]a pathetic boob[/b] at the same time. :D

I was three bodies away from the door when they declared the room "full". :cry:
[COLOR=#FF9900]
I did talk to this person for 2 hours, however.[/COLOR] 
[IMG]http://i453.photobucket.com/albums/qq252/OrangeCatX/DSC01120.jpg[/IMG]
[COLOR=#FF9900]Her voice gets sexier and sexier the longer I watch this series.[/COLOR]

[b]O.o[/b] [size=9](Yes I know it's a dude's voice.)[/size]
</comment>


	<item id="1383825" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="12340" objectname="The Sopranos Trivia Game" username="Quarashi" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 18:21:03 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 18:23:14 +0000" thumbs="5" imageid="50107">
	<body>I am currently finishing up the [b]Sopranos[/b] season 6. I've enjoyed the series as a whole but in a way I kind of look forward to being done with it so I can move on.

[u][b]Recently I have watched:[/b][/u]
[b]Battlestar Galactica [/b]- :star::star::star::star::halfstar: - Which I thought was amazing.
[b]Firefly[/b] - :star::star::star::star::star: - Instantly became my favorite television show alongside ATHF.
[b]Hikaru No Go[/b] - :star::star::star::star::halfstar: - I couldn't stop watching it. It really made me want to play Go even more.
[b]Fullmetal Alchemist: Brotherhood [/b] - :star::star::star::nostar::nostar: - Really enjoyed the first half of the series but then it became stale about half way through.

The next show I might watch will be Death Note.</body>
	
			<comment username="Gamesmeister99" date="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 18:34:38 +0000" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 18:34:38 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 18:34:38 +0000" thumbs="4">
One of the cable channels started today with season one so I watched the first episode this morning, censored of course. "what no frickin ziti" didn't have the same effect for some reason.
</comment>
<comment username="Quarashi" date="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 18:45:31 +0000" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 18:45:31 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 18:45:31 +0000" thumbs="4">
Yeah I couldn't imagine watching the Sopranos censored. It would be like watching the Big Lebowski censored. :shake:
</comment>
<comment username="jtakagi" date="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 01:07:30 +0000" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 01:07:30 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 01:07:30 +0000" thumbs="4">
[q="Quarashi"]Yeah I couldn't imagine watching the Sopranos censored. It would be like watching the Big Lebowski censored. :shake:[/q]

The Big Lebowski is actually pretty amusing censored. 

"This is what happens Larry, when you find a stranger in the Alps!  This is what happens, Larry!"
[youtube=LCcKBcZzGdA]

</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1383848" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="9227" objectname="Weed!" username="Gamesmeister99" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 18:37:55 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 18:37:55 +0000" thumbs="9" imageid="303217">
	<body>My wife and I have been watching weeds since it began (the new season started last week) as well as Rescue Me which has the season finale next week. We are anxiously awaiting season three of Sons of Anarchy (in two weeks) as well as Bones later in the fall. </body>
	
			
		</item>
	<item id="1383859" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="32649" objectname="Madison Trivia" username="boneroller" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 18:49:17 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 18:49:17 +0000" thumbs="13" imageid="0">
	<body>I'm watching tons of television shows, but the one that stands out is Mad Men. I started with Season 1, Episode 1 last week and am currently on Season 4, Episode 3. A couple of more episodes and I'm all caught up.</body>
	
			<comment username="rwinder" date="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 02:22:04 +0000" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 02:22:04 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 02:22:04 +0000" thumbs="2">
Excellent show. I watched on DVD but now that I have caught up, I have to wait for it to show on Sundays at 10.
</comment>
<comment username="Teemu Salohalme" date="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 05:05:01 +0000" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 05:05:01 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 05:05:32 +0000" thumbs="6">
Mad Men just didn't hit here. I couldn't understand, there's no drama, no relatible characters and no story. Well, there's some but not enough for me. You opinion my vary.



</comment>
<comment username="JohnBandettini" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 22:27:50 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 22:27:50 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 22:27:50 +0000" thumbs="6">
Mad men, dull, sorry it just is.
</comment>
<comment username="Vila" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 14:12:47 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 14:12:47 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 14:12:47 +0000" thumbs="2">
I can't get enough of this show. I'm almost done with season 3, and then I'll go back to the start and go through them all again. I'll try and avoid season 4 until it comes out on DVD here, but I'll probably cave.
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1383862" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="3623" objectname="Survivor" username="Gorefeast" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 18:51:39 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 18:51:39 +0000" thumbs="5" imageid="200934">
	<body>I've recently been watching the remake of Survivors, a BBC show about the survivors of a plague that wiped out most of the world's population.  It only lasted two seasons, and apparently ended on a cliffhanger, but the word-of-mouth has been fantastic.

I'm only 2 episodes in, but I'm already hooked.  I love post-apocalyptic shows (Jericho is one of my all-time favorites), so I'm definitely in the target audience.

So far, I'd give it :star::star::star::star:</body>
	
			
		</item>
	<item id="1383863" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="80800" objectname="Curses! of the Vampire" username="eknauer" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 18:51:56 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 18:51:56 +0000" thumbs="9" imageid="793611">
	<body>[i]True Blood, Season 3[/i].  :star::star::star::star::star: This is my favorite season so far behind season 1 and then 2.  This is up there with [i]The Sopranos[/i], [i]Firefly[/i], &amp; [i]Freaks and Geeks[/i] as my all time favorite series.          

[i]Entourage, Season 7[/i]. :star::star::star::star:  Love the punchy 30 minute episodes.  Great glimpse into the Hollywood celebrity lifestyle.  

[i]Mad Men, Season 1[/i]: :star::star::star:  Well made but a bit slow for me.  On the the fence if I'm going to watch additional seasons.        </body>
	
			<comment username="doubtofbuddha" date="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 21:26:34 +0000" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 21:26:34 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 21:26:34 +0000" thumbs="5">
Eric, I have season 2 of Mad Men on DVD if you would like to borrow it! :)
</comment>
<comment username="cylonathalf" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 00:27:20 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 00:27:20 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 00:27:20 +0000" thumbs="6">
[q]True Blood, Season 3. starstarstarstarstar This is my favorite season so far behind season 1 and then 2. [/q]

I just watched the first two seasons this week, glad to hear it rebounds.
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1383866" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="6601" objectname="Murderless Mysteries: Arch Villains Anonymous" username="gschmidl" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 18:54:03 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 18:54:03 +0000" thumbs="5" imageid="26266">
	<body>I'm lazy, so here's a list:

Psych
True Blood
Persons Unknown
Burn Notice
Leverage
Doctor Who
Futurama
Castle</body>
	
			<comment username="boneroller" date="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:08:09 +0000" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:08:09 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:08:09 +0000" thumbs="2">
I feel I must make a comment about Persons Unknown. Whoever writes the scrips should study people more. The reactions to the various situations and each other is what really kills this show for me.
</comment>
<comment username="kendahlj" date="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 20:43:44 +0000" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 20:43:44 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 20:43:44 +0000" thumbs="2">
[q="boneroller"]I feel I must make a comment about Persons Unknown. Whoever writes the scrips should study people more. The reactions to the various situations and each other is what really kills this show for me.[/q]

I gave up on this show after three episodes.  Still curious...but not enough to watch it.  Too many better shows out there.
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1383877" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="36480" objectname="Crown of Roses" username="indigopotter" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:06:55 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:06:55 +0000" thumbs="4" imageid="411471">
	<body>We don't have cable, but we're currently watching Roseanne on DVD. We just started the final season. Roseanne has one of the best series finales ever.</body>
	
			<comment username="Quarashi" date="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:12:20 +0000" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:12:20 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:12:20 +0000" thumbs="3">
Yeah, I don't have cable either. I mostly get stuff from netflix or hulu.
</comment>
<comment username="berserkley" date="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:51:51 +0000" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:51:51 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:51:51 +0000" thumbs="2">
I stopped watching after the third season.
</comment>
<comment username="JohnBandettini" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 22:29:55 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 22:29:55 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 22:30:25 +0000" thumbs="1">
But the last season wasn't actually funny, bit of a problem with a comedy.  :)
</comment>
<comment username="indigopotter" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 01:11:36 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 01:11:36 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 01:11:36 +0000" thumbs="3">
[q="JohnBandettini"]But the last season wasn't actually funny, bit of a problem with a comedy.  :)[/q]

True, there were lots of episodes in the last season I didn't really like, but the series finale, her monologue, is one of the best.
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1383878" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="7471" objectname="Breaking Point" username="Rokkr" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:06:59 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:07:33 +0000" thumbs="11" imageid="30332">
	<body>[IMG]http://www.bite.ca/mtBlog/archives/BreakingBad_title.jpg[/IMG]
Breaking Bad
The successor to The Wire as the best television has to offer.

Set and produced in Albuquerque, New Mexico, Breaking Bad is the story of Walter White (Bryan Cranston), a struggling high school chemistry teacher who is diagnosed with terminal lung cancer at the beginning of the series. He turns to a life of crime, producing and selling methamphetamine with his former student Jesse Pinkman (Aaron Paul) in a desire to secure his family's financial future.</body>
	
			<comment username="HunterJE" date="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:09:03 +0000" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:09:03 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:09:03 +0000" thumbs="4">
I tried so hard.  I even liked it.  But I could only get about four episodes in before the bleakness got to me, and I couldn't watch any further.  I was actually feeling ill after each episode.
</comment>
<comment username="wifwendell" date="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:09:54 +0000" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:09:54 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:09:54 +0000" thumbs="3">
Watched the first two or three on DVD recently.  Well done, but damn depressing.
</comment>
<comment username="TGov" date="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 21:30:22 +0000" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 21:30:22 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 21:30:22 +0000" thumbs="3">
I tried to watch it as well and it was a VERY well done show IMO, but is was just too depressing to watch.  
</comment>
<comment username="ovresmot" date="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 21:56:13 +0000" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 21:56:13 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 21:56:13 +0000" thumbs="2">
I agree with you, Brandon, it's pretty depressing. The episode where Jesse goes to the meth freaks house and sees the little kid just about made me quit watching, but I'm glad I didn't. Best drama of the last 10 years.
</comment>
<comment username="dr_canak" date="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 23:06:27 +0000" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 23:06:27 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 23:06:27 +0000" thumbs="5">
In my opinion,

the best T.V. has to offer at the moment.  You want disturbing, find and rent the Showtime(?) original series "Carnivale".  Now that show had some seriously disturbing shit.

my .02,
jeff
</comment>
<comment username="TGov" date="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 00:25:11 +0000" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 00:25:11 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 00:25:11 +0000" thumbs="2">
I guess part of my problem is that my best friend died of lung cancer and had exactly the same symptoms that the main character has, so I think that makes it doubly hard for me.  It just brings back those memories of his struggle, which isn't the shows fault just a coincidence.  
</comment>
<comment username="moss_icon" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 13:23:44 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 13:23:44 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 13:23:44 +0000" thumbs="2">
definitely the best thing on tv in years. season 2 is absolutely incredible.
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1383880" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="21650" objectname="Wiretap" username="HunterJE" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:08:07 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:08:07 +0000" thumbs="13" imageid="347226">
	<body>Just finished Season 4 of The Wire last night.  Not only the best TV show I've ever seen, but among the top works of literature in any medium.</body>
	
			<comment username="boneroller" date="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:09:40 +0000" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:09:40 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:10:09 +0000" thumbs="4">
I loved The Wire and was very sad when it ended. The only cable show I liked more was Deadwood.
</comment>
<comment username="hermanroozen" date="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 21:25:37 +0000" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 21:25:37 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 21:25:37 +0000" thumbs="2">
Got season 5 lying next to my keyboard right now. At 5-4. Never been so eager to see every single episode since Inspector Morse.
</comment>
<comment username="JohnBandettini" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 22:31:33 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 22:31:33 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 22:31:33 +0000" thumbs="3">
I do like The Wire, but I think The Shield is better.
</comment>
<comment username="everlong205" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 22:58:56 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 22:58:56 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 22:58:56 +0000" thumbs="3">
I heard some negative comments about what some of the main characters do in the last Season, particularly McNulty and how it's out of character. I thought it was rather ingenious, and added an interesting moral depth to some of the charaters (as if they didn't have it already).
Good ending to an interesting show.
</comment>
<comment username="Kafka" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 01:01:47 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 01:01:47 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 01:01:47 +0000" thumbs="3">
I say this all the time and I'll say it here... the 4th season of The Wire is absolutely the best thing that has ever been on TV. Ever. EVER.
</comment>
<comment username="HunterJE" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 06:18:48 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 06:18:48 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 06:18:48 +0000" thumbs="2">
Yeah, having just finished four I can stand by that... wow.
</comment>
<comment username="Teemu Salohalme" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 11:05:20 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 11:05:20 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 11:05:20 +0000" thumbs="2">
Yes, The Wire is exceptionalm,especially seasons 1-3. Season 4 is very good while season 5 might be the weakest: there's a little more suspension of disbelief needed compared to previous seasons but the serial-killer arc is very entertaining when it's starting to get out of McNulty's hands. It's very clever, it just isn't as realistic as all the other seasons before it. 

I think I too like The Shield more. It has consistent quality through-out all the seven seasons and it advances all the time. And it's excruciatingly intense at times. And even the episodic plots were very well written and always somehow original, they didn't repeat themselves. 
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1383907" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="1075" objectname="Big Bang" username="JasonRMax" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:20:28 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:20:28 +0000" thumbs="23" imageid="55241">
	<body>Big Bang Theory

We're watching on DVD so we haven't seen the most recent season but its been a long time since I laughed this hard watching a TV show.  The Christmas gift episode forced me to pause the DVD until my wife and I calmed down enough that we could hear the dialog again.</body>
	
			<comment username="Zen Postman" date="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 03:51:12 +0000" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 03:51:12 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 03:51:12 +0000" thumbs="8">
"I possess the DNA of Leonard Nimoy?!?!"

Hilarious.
</comment>
<comment username="Gargoyle" date="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 06:39:42 +0000" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 06:39:42 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 06:39:42 +0000" thumbs="3">
Brilliant show! And that exact episode had pretty much the same effect on us as well.

Just finished watching the second season again couple days ago. Now waiting for the third season which should ship from Amazon in a month.
</comment>
<comment username="Ploedminka" date="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 10:16:38 +0000" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 10:16:38 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 10:16:38 +0000" thumbs="2">
I'm currently watching the third season, great fun !
</comment>
<comment username="Kwakkie" date="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 11:21:02 +0000" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 11:21:02 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 11:21:02 +0000" thumbs="3">
Everyone seems to love this show. Everyone except me. I actually hate it. Never makes me laugh. Annoying characters. Stupid plot.

It's just not for me.
</comment>
<comment username="Rokkr" date="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 13:34:31 +0000" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 13:34:31 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 13:34:31 +0000" thumbs="3">
It's sad that fans of this show did not watch Aliens in America which was a far better written and much funnier show.
[youtube=jhODwtSimQ4]
</comment>
<comment username="Mease19" date="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 15:39:20 +0000" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 15:39:20 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 15:39:20 +0000" thumbs="4">
If you like The Big Bang Theory, you would also like The IT Crowd.
</comment>
<comment username="JohnBandettini" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 22:32:40 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 22:32:40 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 22:32:40 +0000" thumbs="6">
yeah, it's almost as good as the IT Crowd.  :D
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1383910" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="5555" objectname="White Collar Blues" username="frienetic" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:23:13 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:23:13 +0000" thumbs="8" imageid="21240">
	<body>:star::star::star::star::halfstar:  White Collar (USA) is now in its second season and is one the smartest funniest shows on right now.  I urge all to look it up.  Basically it's as though you took Catch Me if You Can, and then continued the story by turning it into an hour drama show; Con Man that now works for the FBI.  Great stuff and great cast.
:star::star::star:  Rescue Me (FX)  A very gritty show, yet this new season just isn't as great as the first few.  Felt that it was already going down a little from last season, but this one is even more depressing.  It's still great and funny though, when they're just filming the guys in the firehouse making fun of each other and cracking jokes.  A very well produced show though.
</body>
	
			<comment username="Taxers" date="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 22:14:38 +0000" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 22:14:38 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 22:14:38 +0000" thumbs="3">
My wife and I are also watching White Collar.  The scripts are getting better by the show.
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1383928" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="5271" objectname="Stack" username="FrozenHoHos" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:38:12 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:38:12 +0000" thumbs="3" imageid="189550">
	<body>Anything with a :star: I watch with my wife.  :nostar: I fly solo.

[b]Watch regularly and up to date[/b]
:star: True Blood
:star: Man v Food (the kids love this show)
:nostar: Mad Men

[b]Watch intermittently[/b]
:star: Battlestar Galactica (Season 3)
:star: Weeds (Season 3)
:nostar: The Wire (Season 1)

[b]In the queue[/b]
:star: Pillars of the Earth
:nostar: Persons Unknown
:nostar: Rubicon

[b]Will watch when back on the air[/b]
:star: Dexter
:star: Californication

[b]Considering[/b] (a move to Memphis)
The Office
The Tudors
Six Feet Under
It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</body>
	
			<comment username="Quarashi" date="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 12:22:37 +0000" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 12:22:37 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 12:22:37 +0000" thumbs="3">
You really need to finish BSG, Dave.
</comment>
<comment username="FrozenHoHos" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 12:08:49 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 12:08:49 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 12:08:49 +0000" thumbs="3">
Watched another episode last night.

Keep in mind that time we spend with BSG is time away from gaming.  Damned if you do...
</comment>
<comment username="Quarashi" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 19:25:11 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 19:25:11 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 19:25:11 +0000" thumbs="3">
[q="FrozenHoHos"]Keep in mind that time we spend with BSG is time away from gaming.  Damned if you do...[/q]

Let's be honest, you don't play games. :p
</comment>
<comment username="alex352" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 11:35:31 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 11:35:31 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 11:35:31 +0000" thumbs="2">
3rd season BSG is amazing. I still curse myself for having underestimated this show for as long as I did.
</comment>
<comment username="FrozenHoHos" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 17:47:29 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 17:47:29 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 17:47:29 +0000" thumbs="3">
[q="Quarashi"]Let's be honest, you don't play games. :p[/q]
I admit we've hit a bit of a dry spell the last few weeks.  The vacation and a lot of catch up work around the house didn't help any.

Although we did put the kids in front of a movie this afternoon and watched another two episodes.
</comment>
<comment username="SPARTAN VI" date="Thu, 02 Sep 2010 14:27:25 +0000" postdate="Thu, 02 Sep 2010 14:27:25 +0000" editdate="Thu, 02 Sep 2010 14:27:25 +0000" thumbs="2">
[q="FrozenHoHos"][q="Quarashi"]Let's be honest, you don't play games. :p[/q]
I admit we've hit a bit of a dry spell the last few weeks.  The vacation and a lot of catch up work around the house didn't help any.

Although we did put the kids in front of a movie this afternoon and watched another two episodes.[/q]

It all goes down hill from Season 3. Remember BSG for seasons 1 and 2!
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1383939" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="36973" objectname="The Office DVD Board Game" username="jmsmith2434" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:51:47 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:51:47 +0000" thumbs="6" imageid="394439">
	<body>Teh Office.

Everything else currently on tv blows.</body>
	
			<comment username="GodfatherPTS" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 17:23:52 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 17:23:52 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 17:25:54 +0000" thumbs="2">
Current episodes of the Office blow. I gave up on it a long time ago.

I enjoy Modern Family, 30 Rock, and Community much more. Though in its heyday, nothing could top the Office. At its height, I might even suggest it rivaled the British version (well...).
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1383940" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="6022" objectname="13: The Colonies in Revolt" username="ruppt" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:51:50 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:51:50 +0000" thumbs="5" imageid="24822">
	<body>Wharehouse 13

Also:

Burn Notice
Royale Pains
White Collar</body>
	
			<comment username="Arcadious" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 13:24:57 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 13:24:57 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 13:24:57 +0000" thumbs="2">
Warehouse 13 is awesome.
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1383946" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="7152" objectname="The Boss" username="jmsmith2434" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:54:17 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:54:17 +0000" thumbs="4" imageid="579157">
	<body>Although I have been watching reruns of Who's teh Boss?  

Where did the 80's go?</body>
	
			<comment username="Flamin_Jesus" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 09:02:50 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 09:02:50 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 09:02:50 +0000" thumbs="2">
I'd like to know that too, just to guarantee they can't come back. *shudder*
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1383948" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="56787" objectname="Monopoly - Hollywood Edition" username="tiel234" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:56:46 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 19:56:46 +0000" thumbs="5" imageid="561503">
	<body>I'm really liking [b]Entourage [/b]this season. Piven's acting is on point..will Ari survive?!</body>
	
			
		</item>
	<item id="1383956" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="9544" objectname="Batman: The Animated Series; 3D Board Game" username="tlmirkes" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 20:04:54 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 20:04:54 +0000" thumbs="3" imageid="40140">
	<body>I recently got a chance to pick up some series at overstock prices, so I've been working my way through a few shows pretty much concurrently:

ExoSquad
Scrubs
Dead Like Me
Batman: The Animated Series
Mad About You
Transformers (First Generation)

Prior to that, I had a brief binge of Mad Men, catching up on all 3 previous seasons in a matter of two weeks (and in plenty of time to start watching season 4).  Great series, that Mad Men :thumbsup:</body>
	
			
		</item>
	<item id="1383960" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="2640" objectname="Babylon 5 Collectible Card Game" username="bwingrave" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 20:07:37 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 20:07:37 +0000" thumbs="13" imageid="53685">
	<body>I'm watching Babylon 5 again.  It's the first time for my wife and her son, who is eleven years old.  He's really into it, and it's growing on her.  Great long arc story, mystery and sci-fi aspects.  

Felicity.  Good show with lots of character development.

Angel and Buffy the Vampire Slayer.  I'm a big fan of these shows now, but I didn't see them when they were originally on TV.  So this time, I'm watching them in order from the beginning, so I can see how all the crossovers between the shows were intended to be seen.

Veronica Mars.  Good mix of mystery solving and character development.  

Big Bang Theory.  Funny show.  It's rare that my wife and I both like a sitcom.  It helps that she works in a scientific field.

[url=http://www.nbc.com/community/]Community[/url] is the show whose return we're really waiting for.  We were really surprised to find two sitcoms on American TV that were both worth watching.  

Inspector Morse.  I had seen the most recent episodes when they aired on PBS several years ago, and I'm catching up with the older ones as I find them.  The interplay between Morse and his assistant Lewis is great, and some of the mysteries are really twisted.</body>
	
			<comment username="tlmirkes" date="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 20:20:11 +0000" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 20:20:11 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 20:20:11 +0000" thumbs="4">
Oh man, Babylon 5.  My gaming group still goes by various nicknames related to this series and our weekly games of the B5 CCG.  Londo, Carn, PsiCop...  Good times.
</comment>
<comment username="chockle" date="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 01:13:32 +0000" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 01:13:32 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 01:13:32 +0000" thumbs="3">
Watching Babylon 5 with my kid. He laughs at the special effects, but has gotten into the serious tone of it.
</comment>
<comment username="Cazaril" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 02:15:17 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 02:15:17 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 02:15:17 +0000" thumbs="4">
[b]You just picked the BEST of the BEST.[/b]

Take it easy with the family.  I burned out my wife on it over a summer and she still hasn't watched season 4 or 5.  I think we'll just stop at season 4 when she's ready again.

You won't find better writing than this (the ones written by JMS like the ENTIRE season 3).

</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1383998" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="2981" objectname="Breaking Away" username="kendahlj" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 20:48:30 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 20:48:30 +0000" thumbs="5" imageid="151682">
	<body>DAY BREAK (2006, Taye Diggs)

If you missed it when it was on ABC, and most people did and it got cancelled midseason, then you need to get the DVD set.  In my top five of favorite TV shows of all time.  I challenge anyone to watch it and not like it.  Okay, actually if you aren't a fan of action and intrigue you might not like it. And if you hated the concept of Groundhog's Day then you might not like it, although it's different.

It's about a cop who is framed for murder.  He wakes up everyday and it's the same day.  So each day he gets a few more clues to the mystery.  Excellent writing...

</body>
	
			<comment username="Scurra" date="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 12:10:45 +0000" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 12:10:45 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 12:10:45 +0000" thumbs="2">
Absolutely.
One of the best arguments that there is space for "single season" shows in recent years ([i]Harpers Island[/i] is another.)  
Sometimes you need more than a Miniseries to tell a story, but you don't need multiple seasons.  A lesson which [i]Dollhouse [/i]and [i]Flash Forward[/i] could have benefited from - both of them could have been sensational if they hadn't needed to be on-going...
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1384017" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="3369" objectname="John Carter: Warlord of Mars" username="alsandor" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 21:13:10 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 21:13:10 +0000" thumbs="6" imageid="10710">
	<body>[b]Life on Mars[/b], the UK version.

</body>
	
			<comment username="boneroller" date="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 21:37:03 +0000" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 21:37:03 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 21:37:03 +0000" thumbs="2">
Then you'll have to sit through 3 seasons of Ashes To Ashes to find out what it all means.
</comment>
<comment username="JohnBandettini" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 22:37:07 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 22:37:07 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 22:37:07 +0000" thumbs="3">
When I saw this I was really hoping there was a John Carter TV series.  :cry:
</comment>
<comment username="Donalsligo" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 11:39:10 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 11:39:10 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 11:39:10 +0000" thumbs="2">
DCI Gene Hunt.......simply the best character ever on TV.

Sam, Raymondo, Chris, Shazza, Alex.....all a wonderful supporting cast.

As the great man himself would say "Fandabadozy".

(And a wonderful soundtrack).
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1384024" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="8023" objectname="Faces in the Crowd" username="thomcat" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 21:20:30 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 21:20:30 +0000" thumbs="10" imageid="73416">
	<body>Can't believe I am the first to add "The I.T. Crowd", a UK comedy that just finished it's fourth series. The first 3 series are available on NetFlix, for those on this side of the pond.

Currently also watching Foyle's War, up to series 4 or 5 (depending on US or British notation).</body>
	
			<comment username="bwingrave" date="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 22:17:32 +0000" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 22:17:32 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 22:17:32 +0000" thumbs="2">
I liked Foyle's War a lot.  

Could not get into The I.T. Crowd though.  My wife and I gave up after two episodes.  Just not our kind of humor.  
</comment>
<comment username="historysteph" date="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 01:00:43 +0000" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 01:00:43 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 01:00:43 +0000" thumbs="2">
Foyle's War is amazing.  I tried the IT Crowd as well, but couldn't get into it.
</comment>
<comment username="Dino25" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 15:22:34 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 15:22:34 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 15:22:34 +0000" thumbs="2">
This is the one I was going to add. This and Frasier are my favorite comedies. I wish the current season was as wonderful as the other three. 
</comment>
<comment username="remus" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 03:59:37 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 03:59:37 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 03:59:37 +0000" thumbs="2">
I like the IT crowd.  I've only watched the first two seasons.  Didn't know there were more.  I'll look for Season 3 on Netflix, thanks.
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1384050" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="23866" objectname="Buck Rogers Game: Adventures in the 25th Century" username="Frankenfletch" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 21:41:42 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 21:41:42 +0000" thumbs="6" imageid="128502">
	<body>I picked up the [b]Buck Rogers[/b] series recently at Wally world for $15. So far it's the best $15 I ever spent on a show.  I'm half way through it and [b]LOVING IT[/b]!

And of course the only current show I'm following is the new season of  [b]Futurama[/b].

There have been some briliant episodes and some not so great episodes but I'm soooooo glad it's finally back!</body>
	
			<comment username="ovresmot" date="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 22:00:48 +0000" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 22:00:48 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 22:00:48 +0000" thumbs="4">
The episode with the Vorvon and Commander Deering in that satin uniform was the first time I was vividly aware of the differences between boys and girls! Great show (die Twikki die!)  :D
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1384084" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="32732" objectname="Daily Mail Footer-Pool" username="ixnay66" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 22:06:25 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 22:06:25 +0000" thumbs="8" imageid="265502">
	<body>I watch the Daily Show every night and also watch Eureka.</body>
	
			
		</item>
	<item id="1384144" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="25695" objectname="Chopstick Dexterity MegaChallenge 3000" username="mjacobsca" postdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 23:04:32 +0000" editdate="Thu, 26 Aug 2010 23:04:32 +0000" thumbs="7" imageid="258318">
	<body>[b]Chopped[/b]

My guilty pleasure right now is [i]Chopped[/i], on the food network. I can't get enough of this show...</body>
	
			<comment username="SPARTAN VI" date="Thu, 02 Sep 2010 14:29:12 +0000" postdate="Thu, 02 Sep 2010 14:29:12 +0000" editdate="Thu, 02 Sep 2010 14:29:37 +0000" thumbs="2">
Diners Drive-ins and Dives. I don't know why I torture by myself watching Guy eat all that delicious food. :cry:
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1384223" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="20209" objectname="Serial Killer: The Board Game" username="stormseeker75" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 00:20:25 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 00:20:25 +0000" thumbs="5" imageid="109793">
	<body>We are on the 6th episode of Dexter: Season 3.  I loved the first 2 seasons but this one is not working for me.  I'll stick with it though.

Next up is Pillars of the Earth.</body>
	
			<comment username="Liggur" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 23:37:14 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 23:37:14 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 23:37:14 +0000" thumbs="2">
Just watched Season 4, Episode 1 on FX On demand.
Good Stuff!
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1384254" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="37111" objectname="Battlestar Galactica" username="Tompy" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 01:16:53 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 01:16:53 +0000" thumbs="3" imageid="354500">
	<body>I thought the  miniseries was excellent.  I'm early in season 1 still and have to say the first couple of episodes are not nearly as good as the miniseries.  I've heard good things so I assume things build up and really get going.

One of the reasons I like it is the characters are not always, actually rarely, comfortable with themselves or each other.</body>
	
			<comment username="airjudden" date="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 05:28:30 +0000" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 05:28:30 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 05:28:30 +0000" thumbs="8">
Wow -- if you didn't like the first episode ("33"), this show may not be for you.  33 is one of the best episodes of the entire show.
</comment>
<comment username="Dino25" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 15:25:04 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 15:25:04 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 15:35:09 +0000" thumbs="2">
This is one of my husbands favorite shows but I feel like I am too far behind to start watching it and there are too many episodes to start from the beginning.
</comment>
<comment username="GodfatherPTS" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 17:28:13 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 17:28:13 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 17:28:13 +0000" thumbs="3">
[q="airjudden"]Wow -- if you didn't like the first episode ("33"), this show may not be for you.  33 is one of the best episodes of the entire show.[/q]

I think that episode is one of the best single TV episodes of any series EVER. That one blew me away. Was hooked on BSG immediately.
</comment>
<comment username="manutd03" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 00:12:07 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 00:12:07 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 00:12:07 +0000" thumbs="2">
[q="GodfatherPTS"][q="airjudden"]Wow -- if you didn't like the first episode ("33"), this show may not be for you.  33 is one of the best episodes of the entire show.[/q]

I think that episode is one of the best single TV episodes of any series EVER. That one blew me away. Was hooked on BSG immediately.[/q]

Yeah, I'm only in the middle of Season 2, and I think "33" was probably the best episode so far.  Fantastic.
</comment>
<comment username="alex352" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 11:40:56 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 11:40:56 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 11:40:56 +0000" thumbs="2">
[q="manutd03"][q="GodfatherPTS"][q="airjudden"]Wow -- if you didn't like the first episode ("33"), this show may not be for you.  33 is one of the best episodes of the entire show.[/q]

I think that episode is one of the best single TV episodes of any series EVER. That one blew me away. Was hooked on BSG immediately.[/q]

Yeah, I'm only in the middle of Season 2, and I think "33" was probably the best episode so far.  Fantastic.[/q]

Wait till season 3... :D 

Regarding the OP: I think the show can take a while to really drag you in. The characters constantly evolve and so does their relationships. Stick with it and I think you won't regret it.
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1384255" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="2513" objectname="Colony" username="chockle" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 01:16:58 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 15:29:26 +0000" thumbs="5" imageid="30888">
	<body>A friend of mine is on [b]The Colony[/b] this season. One day he said he'd be gone for 10 weeks, couldn't talk about it, and could he store his computer at my place in case his apartment gets broken into.
George:
[ImageID=794384 small]</body>
	
			<comment username="bdean152" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 19:44:14 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 19:44:14 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 19:44:14 +0000" thumbs="2">
Me too!
Downloaded the first season to supplement week to week.

</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1384315" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="12014" objectname="Social Lies" username="HamsterOfFury" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 02:34:10 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 02:36:21 +0000" thumbs="4" imageid="48426">
	<body>In Japan I have very little choice of English language shows as I am limited to Fox Japan, Super Drama TV and AXN (CSIs mostly) and their Mystery Channel (which does have Monk, Poirot and Jonathan Creek amongst their chunk of German and French shows).

However this has meant that I've been able to discover the excellent Third Watch, NCIS, Mental, House and numerous others over the last couple of years.

Currently though my big winners are:


Lie To Me
Burn Notice
NCIS

Simpsons is just about to start airing at 10pm on Sunday nights which is good as I'm at work in their old 6pm slot.


EDIT: Also, through downloads I've been watching through Farscape with my wife. I watched it when I was younger but to watch the entire thing through in its entirity (we're about 6 episodes into season 4) has been a delight. Definitely my favourite sci-fi show.</body>
	
			<comment username="Teemu Salohalme" date="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 05:02:49 +0000" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 05:02:49 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 05:03:04 +0000" thumbs="2">
Oh, Farscape. I remember when I was for the first time watching the last four episodes of season two. I remember thinking, "did they really do that" many times during those episodes - the infestation of Moya, the bank robbery and yes, the whole Die Me, Dichotomy.

Two season four episodes, Lava's A Many Splendored Thing and I Shrink, Therefore I Am, made me laugh my ass off.
</comment>
<comment username="Dujo" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 03:51:14 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 03:51:14 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 03:51:14 +0000" thumbs="2">
I came here for Lie to Me.
</comment>
<comment username="HamsterOfFury" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 08:46:35 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 08:46:35 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 08:46:35 +0000" thumbs="2">
I THINK my favourite Farscape episode is actually Scratch n Sniff which was more of a comedy episode. Loads of weird cuts around and told as a story from Crichton to Pilot as to why he's back on the ship and not on "shore leave".
Some people don't like it so much, I know, but it amused me.

There are better story episodes but that one makes me giggle.
</comment>
<comment username="Teemu Salohalme" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 11:10:15 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 11:10:15 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 11:10:38 +0000" thumbs="2">
I agree, Scratch n Sniff is clever and one of the best comedic and one of best of those really weird episodes Farscape did so well.

I still think one of the most cleverly and brilliantly acted episodes of Farscape is The Ugly Truth. There the same story is told from Stark's, D'Argo's and John's perspective. They all tell the exact story how they thought it went: John thought he was the leader while in D'Argo's version John was just a whining and scary man while D'Argo himself was the true leader. And so forth. It's a great episode but there's some many of those in Farscape. 

Oh, how I miss it.



</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1384376" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="217" objectname="A la carte" username="DarrinWilliams" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 03:48:38 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 03:49:48 +0000" thumbs="6" imageid="599251">
	<body>We watch a lot of Food Network at my place.

When we're not watching people cook things that I'd never eat, I like:

[b]Castle [/b]- Moonlighting for this generation

[b]Fringe [/b]- Walter makes the show

[b]Psych [/b]- Back on track after a bad season

[b]Big Bang[/b] - Waiting for Season 3 on DVD

Of course, now that it's fall, I'll be watching [b]Football [/b]at the NFL, College and Texas High School level. (Football is something special around these parts.)</body>
	
			<comment username="edelen" date="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 12:42:24 +0000" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 12:42:24 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 12:42:24 +0000" thumbs="3">
I watch Fringe, too. The only thing I do watch on TV. And I find it amusing that Torv and Noble, both Australians, carry the show. I guess I'm not used to Australians doing American accents on my TV. Films, yeah. TV seems like a whole 'nother medium, though.
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1384421" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="3955" objectname="Bang!" username="Teemu Salohalme" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 04:56:59 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 04:56:59 +0000" thumbs="4" imageid="174405">
	<body>We, me and my wife, are currently watching

[b]Justified[/b] :star::star::star::star::halfstar:
So far, I've enjoyed Justified enormously and it's my latest favorite of new shows. Timothy Olyphant is just fantastic as Givens. Walton Goggins demonstrates his terrific acting skills as Boyd like he did in The Shield. What I like the most in Justied is the attitude and the irony how the characters respond to everything. This has incredibly well written and clever dialogue. Though mainly episodic in format, Justified kept it's quality through-out the season, with only one or two hiccups.

[b]Damages[/b] :star::star::star::star::star:
Saved for the seasons four and five! Season three was the best yet, right before season one. Season two was a bit of a letdown but the latest season came back to the top with it's superb cast - Martin Short was just perfect for the role of Leonard Winstone, beautifully acted. And naturally Glenn Close continues to shine as Patricia Hewes. The mystery was also very interesting but even more interesting part of the season was to watch the decline of a rich and famous family.

[b]Human Target[/b] :star::star::star::halfstar:
Not even near the greatness of previous two shows, Human Target represents perfect escapism. It does with a tv budget what some movies do with a movie budget, week after week. Yes, during the first season there were some terrible episodes but mostly it was a extremely fun ride. 

[b]Boston Legal[/b] :star::star::star:
I watched the first two seasons this summer and got bored when the same sexistic and sometimes stupid jokes were repeated episode after episode. Every four or five episodes Alan ja Denny argued and patched up their relationship by the end of the episode to get to sit on the balcony. The show seemed to go nowhere and the characters didn't have decent drama - or when they almost did, Kelley dropped them from the show. What is that? Boston Legal was at occasionally very funny and entertaining but too often it was not.

[b]In Treatment[/b] :star::star::star::star::star:
Exceptional show, watching season two now. Sad and smart. This gets right into my head and heart. Acting is something you don't see anywhere else. Luckily they are making season three.

And starting this coming season:

[b]No Ordinary Family[/b], [b]Event[/b] and at least for the pilot [b]Undercovers[/b].</body>
	
			<comment username="Dino25" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 15:28:08 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 15:28:08 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 15:28:08 +0000" thumbs="2">
I watched one episode (the one where from what I can remember a man kills his wife with a frying pan) and loved it so much I am surprised I didn't watch any more. From your comments, sounds like I watched most of them. It was a great episode though.
</comment>
<comment username="elgin_j" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 19:49:20 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 19:49:20 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 19:49:20 +0000" thumbs="0">
Justified is very good but very dry - I think it is the type of programme that will improve with a second viewing...
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1384449" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="3765" objectname="Babylon 5 Wars" username="airjudden" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 05:27:36 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 05:36:52 +0000" thumbs="12" imageid="52504">
	<body>I work out at lunchtime with the PS2 (similar to WiiFit).  Problem is, I'm bored when I do it.  I need to keep my mind engaged for the 48 minute workout.

So I set up the PS2 on a little TV.  On the Big TV next to it, I have B5 set up.  B5 episodes are 44 minutes -- it's like it's meant to be.

How do I like it?  Well, it's my 5th time going through the show.  I had Season 5's theme music played at my wedding.  I named one of my children after one of the characters.  When telemarketers used to call, I would either play the part of Kosh (confuse the heck out of them), Morden (continually ask them "What do you want?") or Mr. Sebasitian, the Vorlon inquisitor (keep asking them "Who are you?" and use all of his little insults, such as, "You want me to switch my long distance to AT&amp;T when you cannot answer the simplest questions without falling back on names, job titles, religious affiliations, and those things that others give to you when you choose to hide behind formalities.  Have you nothing of your own -- nothing to stand on that isn't provided, defined, delineated, stamped, sanitized, numbered and approved by others?  Who are you?   You were destined to be the nail that gets beaten down by the hammer: bang, bang, BANG!")

Yeah, I'd say it's only the greatest TV show of all time.

What's next?  Battlestar Galactica.  Watching them back-to-back, I will finally be able to see how they compare to each other.

Also currently watching J.A.G.  (Season 2), NCIS (Season 7), and Curb Your Enthusiasm (Season 7).</body>
	
			<comment username="dwashba" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 02:13:09 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 02:13:09 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 02:13:09 +0000" thumbs="3">
Dude you win. You win at being geek. That is amazing. I am not even going to say anything else but thats cool.
</comment>
<comment username="Cazaril" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 02:17:45 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 02:17:45 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 02:17:45 +0000" thumbs="2">
Unbelievable - and I thought I was a huge fan.

I still quote from the show, think about the show, and remember it in vivid detail.

No other TV series has changed me like Babylon 5.


</comment>
<comment username="alex352" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 11:44:41 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 11:44:41 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 11:44:41 +0000" thumbs="2">
Give us your phone number! I'll call you petending to be a telemarketer just for the experience... Sounds AMAZING!
</comment>
<comment username="airjudden" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 16:53:10 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 16:53:10 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 16:54:58 +0000" thumbs="4">
Since the government created the no-call list, I rarely get any calls, so I'm really out of practice. (I wrote down some of my favorite conversations to amuse myself). Here is how I worked Kosh. Note, I used to mimic his voice perfectly (TM = Telemarketer):

TM: This is AT&amp;T. We understand that you used to be a customer, and now you are not. May I ask who you are with?

Me: Gold Channel

TM: I have not heard of them.

Me: We use organic technology. It is ... efficient.

TM: OK. How much do you spend on your long distance calls?

Me: Nothing.

TM: Nothing? How is that?

Me: The Vorlon government pays.

TM: Do you know how much they pay?

Me: The truth points to itself.

TM: Huh? I don't understand.

Me: Understanding is three-edged sword. Do you understand?

TM: No

Me: Goooooood.

TM: Do you make international calls?

Me: I make intergalactic calls.

TM: What planet do you call?

Me: Vorlon Homeworld

TM: What planet are you on now?

Me: Earth.

TM: How do you handle local calls?

Me: Telepathy.

TM: Can you explain?

Me: Do you seek meaning?

TM: Yes.

Me: Then listen to the music and not to the song.

TM: What do you want out of your long distance service?

Me: Never ask that question.

TM: OK -- would you be interested in saving money for your government?

Me: No.

TM: Why not?

Me: The avalache has started. It is too late for the pebbles to vote. 

TM: Do you realize that AT&amp;T has been voted the top long distance carrier?

Me: A stroke of the brush does not guarantee art from the bristles.

TM: Alright... Well, is 'Gold Channel' meeting all of your long distance needs?

Me: What is need compared to the path?

TM: Ummm...

Me: You may call again at the hour of scampering.

TM: When is that?

Me: No more questions.

*Click* 
</comment>
<comment username="alex352" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 17:23:03 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 17:23:03 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 17:23:03 +0000" thumbs="2">
Man, this is hillarious. You have to give the guy credit, though, for not giving up easily. 
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1384500" objecttype="family" subtype="rpg" objectid="798" objectname="The Burning Wheel (Revised Edition)" username="MJ Harnish" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 07:22:41 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 07:22:41 +0000" thumbs="7" imageid="514464">
	<body>Living in Germany, I watch TV shows only intermittently, largely as DVDs while I'm working on something else on my computer - thus I'm not always the most intense or attentive watcher. I also tend to be behind the current hotness since I'm working from DVDs/iTunes. In 2010, some of the stuff I watched included:

[b]Good[/b]
* Burn Notice, Season 1 - I really like it so far

* Sons of Anarchy, Seasons 1 &amp; 2 - very good; reminds me of the Shield. 

* Big Bang Theory, seasons 1 &amp; 2 - great stuff; I watched S1 &amp; 2

* How I met your mother, season 1 - another great one I started watching on DVD. I've only watched S1 so far so I'm not sure if it holds up.

* Dollhouse, season 1 - watched S1 and after a somewhat uneven start, it got really, really great. Am now waiting on S2. It's a shame it only will stick around for 2 seasons, but better that then turn in to Lost.

* Leverage, season 1 - I like it. It's not great, but the pilot was excellent and the shows are interesting. It's funny that the "bad guys turning good" theme, which was popular in the 1980s, has now come back around.

*Castle, season 1 - Liked this one a lot. I was a sucker for murder/crime mystery shows and this is hearkening back to the 80's again.

[b]So-so[/b]
* Lost, Season 3-6 - I actually got through the last 4 seasons over the summer while writing. Season 3 &amp; 4 were good (but not as good as the first 2), but 5 &amp; 6 didn't work at all for me.

* BSG, Season 3 - I loved S1 when I watched it a few years ago. S2 was okay (watched it last year); S3 just bores the hell out of me; the plot developments are vague and many of the episodes are completely forgettable IMO. I probably won't bother watching beyond season 3.

* Buffy, Season 4 - I have a love/hate relationship with Buffy; I love the overall story but the individual episodes are up and down.

[b]Bad[/b]
* Heroes, Season 3 - the whole show seems to be all about retconning the first season (which I really liked) over and over; at this point it's gotten boring.

[b]Up next[/b]
Dexter, season 2; Burn Notice, season 2; Breaking Bad, season 1.</body>
	
			
		</item>
	<item id="1384516" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="36920" objectname="Rules of Engagement" username="Double B" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 07:48:12 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 07:48:12 +0000" thumbs="5" imageid="505398">
	<body>I watch most of the series with my boyfriend and currently favourite is definitely [b]Rules of engagement. [/b]Every character is well "made", has his own opinions which make you laugh :) It's a great one when you only have half an hour off and really need something to just cheer up and enjoy.

The next one, which we just discovered is [b]The IT crowd[/b]. Well, this one really is something special :D English humor, and a good one :) First I thought I won't like it, since I'm not that much into it, but it's really good. 

I alone watch House, which is getting better and better for me.

Those that we are trying to watch, but mostly fall asleep while at it, are Stargate universe (this one really sucks), there were heroes (thank god that's over) and Dexter and Lie to me (don't get the excitement over those two).
</body>
	
			<comment username="Kafka" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 14:28:28 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 14:28:28 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 14:28:28 +0000" thumbs="3">
The first episode of the 2nd season of The IT Crowd (the one where they go to the theater to see "GAY!") is one of the funniest things I have ever seen on TV.
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1384551" objecttype="thing" subtype="rpgitem" objectid="63652" objectname="Doctor Who: Adventures in Time and Space: The Roleplaying Game (10th Doctor)" username="Kwakkie" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 08:45:24 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 08:45:24 +0000" thumbs="5" imageid="624244">
	<body>A little late to the party. Started watching 3 months ago. And I LOVE it. Just finished season 2 of the new series. I'd recommend it to anyone, even if they are not into scifi.

I'm also watching Torchwood (the spin-off). But I don't like it as much as Doctor Who. The content is more mature. Usually this isn't a problem for me. It is a problem for me if they show more mature content just for the sake of it. I also prefer Jack as he was in Doctor Who. Only saw the first 2 of the first season though...</body>
	
			<comment username="ekted" date="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 16:27:43 +0000" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 16:27:43 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 16:27:43 +0000" thumbs="6">
I'm watching [b]Doctor Who[/b] as well, along with:

[b]30 Rock

Big Bang Theory

Bones

Family Guy

House

Numb3rs

Sherlock

The Closer[/b]
</comment>
<comment username="Wulf Corbett" date="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 18:45:59 +0000" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 18:45:59 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 18:45:59 +0000" thumbs="4">
Torchwood Season 1 was almost a writeoff... Season 2, however, was excellent! As you say, it tried way [i]way[/i] too hard in the beginning to be [i]really really not Doctor Who[/i]... Stick with it, there's good stuff in there.
</comment>
<comment username="Kwakkie" date="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 20:09:56 +0000" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 20:09:56 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 20:09:56 +0000" thumbs="2">
Thanks for the heads up.

I don't think I'll watch it in release order though. I'll probably watch all of Doctor Who first, and then Torchwood (and maybe sarah jane as well?).
</comment>
<comment username="Wulf Corbett" date="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 20:13:08 +0000" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 20:13:08 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 20:13:08 +0000" thumbs="4">
[q="Kwakkie"](and maybe sarah jane as well?).[/q]I cannot praise The Sarah Jane Adventures highly enough. This is what the [i]old[/i] Doctor Who wanted to be, if only it had had the budget! It's one of the finest bits of children's TV I've seen as an adult (maybe my opinion as a child would have been different...)
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1384552" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="327" objectname="Loopin' Louie" username="Hirocon" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 08:45:55 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 08:45:55 +0000" thumbs="5" imageid="289639">
	<body>I'm watching the first season of [url=http://vod.fxnetworks.com/watch/louie/]Louie[/url] on the FX Network website.</body>
	
			<comment username="remus" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 04:02:53 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 04:02:53 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 04:02:53 +0000" thumbs="3">
Great show!  Louis C.K. is hillarious.  I'm a big fan of his HBO sitcom Lucky Louie.
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1384606" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="20821" objectname="Tara, Seat of Kings" username="Ozludo" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 10:35:37 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 10:35:37 +0000" thumbs="5" imageid="147787">
	<body>
[b]United States of Tara[/b]
Toni Collette is so good in this. The rest of the cast are also excellent, but the whole is much greater than the sum of its parts. All the characters are multifaceted, the direction and set dressing are exemplary, and the plot... oh boy. TV that is constantly engaging.

-R
</body>
	
			
		</item>
	<item id="1384632" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="2511" objectname="Sherlock Holmes Consulting Detective" username="Scurra" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 12:18:56 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 12:18:56 +0000" thumbs="10" imageid="162479">
	<body>[b]Sherlock[/b]
Yes, I know we've had several perfectly good updates of Sherlock Holmes in recent years ([i]House [/i]being perhaps the most obvious) but this was something else again.  Spectacularly good writing, direction and performances combined to make this feel utterly new and yet completely true to the original.  Much as I enjoyed the Ritchie movie, this did a much better job of redefining the character for today.</body>
	
			<comment username="Rokkr" date="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 13:45:38 +0000" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 13:45:38 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 13:45:38 +0000" thumbs="2">
This is an excellent show. But 3 episodes is way too short for one season and the cliff hanger is killing me.
</comment>
<comment username="Ugavine" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 00:12:53 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 00:12:53 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 00:12:53 +0000" thumbs="2">

I vey much enjoyed this.  Although it was mainly for Martin Freeman, I thought he was excellent as Watson.
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1384849" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="28838" objectname="Bleach TCG" username="J.L.Robert" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 16:55:36 +0000" editdate="Wed, 01 Sep 2010 04:38:59 +0000" thumbs="5" imageid="200940">
	<body>I don't like watching TV on my computer, so streaming is not for me.  I stick with what's directly on the idiot-box.

Alphabetically, I'm currently watching:

[b]Being Human[/b] (BBC America) - I'm not much of a modern horror genre fan, but this is a really well-made series.
[b]English Premier League Football[/b] (Fox Soccer Channel and ESPN 2)
[b]Great Food Truck Race[/b] (Food TV) - Corny, but entertaining.
[b]Pardon the Interruption[/b] (ESPN) - My daily sports fix...when it's on.
[b]Project Runway[/b] (Lifetime) - I've been watching since the very first season.
[b]The Choir[/b] (BBC America) - This show shames Glee. The most inspirational TV I've seen in YEARS.
[b]Top Chef[/b] (Bravo) - This season seems weaker than the past, with nobody to really root for.


Also alphabetically, I'm awaiting new episodes of:

[b]Bleach[/b] (Adult Swim--Tomorrow night! Yay!) - Anime/soap opera. But fun.
[b]Robot Chicken[/b] (Adult Swim) - They can't make enough of this!
[b]Survivor[/b] (CBS) - Waiting to see Jimmy Johnson this season.
[b]The Amazing Race[/b] (CBS) - Love seeing the little slices of the world this show provides.
[b]The Ultimate Fighter[/b] (Spike TV) - Love MMA. And this competition show is pure competition...win or go home.
[b]The Venture Brothers[/b] (Adult Swim) - It's grown on me over the years.
[b]Top Gear[/b] (BBC America) - Fun show, even for non-gearheads like myself.</body>
	
			<comment username="Wulf Corbett" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 15:29:53 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 15:29:53 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 15:29:53 +0000" thumbs="3">
[b]Being Human[/b] was a bit of a trial for me. It starts out not sure if it's comedy or drama, moves into angsty drama, and ends up quite brutal horror... Good, well-made series, but a bit lacking in... I don't know... direction?... in early stages.
</comment>
<comment username="GodfatherPTS" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 17:44:43 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 17:44:43 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 17:44:43 +0000" thumbs="3">
I watch [b]PTI[/b] all the time as well. "When its on". For me this means when Wilbon and Kornheiser are both on the show. Sometimes when one is missing, I just turn it off. Sadly, this happens more and more these days.
</comment>
<comment username="lmlawson" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 01:05:30 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 01:05:30 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 01:05:30 +0000" thumbs="3">
[q]Survivor (CBS) - Waiting to see Jimmy Johnson this season.[/q]

I'm a faithful Survivor fan, but this might keep me from watching!  :p
</comment>
<comment username="J.L.Robert" date="Mon, 30 Aug 2010 00:23:52 +0000" postdate="Mon, 30 Aug 2010 00:23:52 +0000" editdate="Mon, 30 Aug 2010 00:23:52 +0000" thumbs="2">
[q="Wulf Corbett"][b]Being Human[/b] was a bit of a trial for me. It starts out not sure if it's comedy or drama, moves into angsty drama, and ends up quite brutal horror... Good, well-made series, but a bit lacking in... I don't know... direction?... in early stages.[/q]

I'll admit that having so many divergent storylines did make the show difficult to follow at first.  But at least the characters are being portrayed as something other than brooding, emo-types, which seems to be the only way to portray supernatural beings these days.
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1384954" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="6022" objectname="13: The Colonies in Revolt" username="deacondavid" postdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 18:42:14 +0000" editdate="Fri, 27 Aug 2010 18:42:14 +0000" thumbs="3" imageid="24822">
	<body>Currently, it's summer, which lessens the on-air options. My wife and I are watching:

Warehouse 13 - an entertaining series that is very hard to describe.
White Collar - A well-written show. I like someone else's description above of it being "Catch Me If You Can where the con man goes to work for the FBI"
Pillars of the Earth - I really like the book. The mini-series captures the feel, though it is not as good as I had hoped.
Farscape - We're currently in season 3, a long time after we had watched season 2. There's some interesting stuff going on, but it has been so long since we saw the earlier seasons that we are sometimes lost.
Psych - I agree that this season is going much better than the last one.

Just finished:
Top Gear - I am, by no means, a car enthusiast (two Hondas in our family, one a hybrid). Still, this show makes me laugh - sometimes very hard.
The Middle Man - This show flew underneath our radar, having come and gone before we discovered it. Kind of a "Men in Black" mash-up with tons of clever science fiction references thrown in asides. Was probably on the wrong network to have stood a chance of making it. There are only twelve episodes and I highly recommend it.
The IT Crowd - Am I the target audience for this? Yes, I am and I love it.

Up next:
Farscape season 4
Futurama, possibly (I've been saving the new season up for a viewing binge)
Then the new season - Big Bang Theory (the best show on the air right now) can't return soon enough. There will be others watched, but this is the one that I'm really looking forward to in the new season...</body>
	
			<comment username="GodfatherPTS" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 17:30:04 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 17:30:04 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 17:30:04 +0000" thumbs="3">
I used to record Top Gear episodes on my DVR, until I started seeing repeats all the time. I have to say, this is one fine show. Give it a look, even if you aren't a car enthusiast. Well made program!
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1385172" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="11155" objectname="How To Be A Complete Bastard" username="Ugavine" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 00:04:17 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 00:04:17 +0000" thumbs="3" imageid="45390">
	<body>Ironically it's Ade's comedy partner I'm currently watching;

[b]The New Statesman[/b]

We're (my girlfriend and I) just in the middle of [i]Who Shot B'stard?[/i]
Not Rik Mayalls best series but still very funny.  But it takes a lot of thinking back to the politcs of the time as a lot of jokes were topical.</body>
	
			
		</item>
	<item id="1385177" objecttype="thing" subtype="rpgitem" objectid="73275" objectname="Bloodsand Arena" username="Ugavine" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 00:08:41 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 00:08:41 +0000" thumbs="5" imageid="747462">
	<body>[b]Spartacus: Blood and Sand[/b]

Just got the end of the 1st series.  It's tacky with terrible lines and questionable acting.  The fight scenes are totally over the top with blood and gore galore.  It's unadulterated sex and violence with plenty of both.  
Certainly a series I'll be buying on DVD. :D</body>
	
			<comment username="elgin_j" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 19:52:39 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 19:52:39 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 19:52:39 +0000" thumbs="2">
Spartacus is f**king awesome!!!
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1385179" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="35726" objectname="Torchwood TCG" username="Ugavine" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 00:11:40 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 00:11:40 +0000" thumbs="4" imageid="760740">
	<body>[b]Torchwood[/b]

Love Doctor Who.  Love Torchwood.  John Barrowman is just fantastic (I got to see him in panto last year).  It's been a while since this was on so we thgouht we'd rewatch the DVDs.  I've still got the Series 2 DVDs unwatched (I did watch it on TV).</body>
	
			
		</item>
	<item id="1385227" objecttype="family" subtype="rpg" objectid="734" objectname="Angel Role-playing Game" username="dwashba" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 02:07:29 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 02:07:29 +0000" thumbs="5" imageid="528136">
	<body>On the fourth season its kinda slow right now about halfway through. I think season 3 was better. :D</body>
	
			<comment username="geschichte" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 03:32:26 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 03:32:26 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 03:32:26 +0000" thumbs="3">
Season 5 is amazing.
</comment>
<comment username="dwashba" date="Sat, 26 Mar 2011 19:52:10 +0000" postdate="Sat, 26 Mar 2011 19:52:10 +0000" editdate="Sat, 26 Mar 2011 19:52:10 +0000" thumbs="2">
I agree, the finally was incredible...so was the rest of the season. Don't think the follow up comics are all that good. Just meh.
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1385451" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="9482" objectname="Flashback" username="Xelforp" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 12:36:29 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 12:36:29 +0000" thumbs="3" imageid="64285">
	<body>The only tv show that I've watched this year is [b]Flash Forward[/b]. Still have to see the last episode, but have enjoyed this show. Too bad (or perhaps good) that it discontinued.
</body>
	
			
		</item>
	<item id="1385526" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="35815" objectname="A Touch of Evil: The Supernatural Game" username="Myrdin T Sasnak" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 14:20:47 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 14:20:47 +0000" thumbs="5" imageid="326493">
	<body>[b]Supernatural[/b]
My wife and I are Netflixing this trying to catch up. We're up to the second disc for season 4 so far - almost there! It's been real neat only having to wait a day or two between season ending cliffhangers instead of the usual 4 or 5 months. A really great series with great acting and chemistry amongst the actors. Great story arcs. Nifty blend of humor with the drama and the horror, too. Season 5 is available in September. Will have to record season 6 until we see all of season 5. </body>
	
			<comment username="evil_puck" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 15:14:47 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 15:14:47 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 15:14:47 +0000" thumbs="2">
nice series but ,..after 5 seasons and 32499234 they piss each other off and parted their ways it is getting a litte repetitive...

the original author will not make season 6...i have bad feelings about this...
</comment>
<comment username="elgin_j" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 19:55:13 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 19:55:13 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 19:55:13 +0000" thumbs="1">
[q="evil_puck"]nice series but ,..after 5 seasons and 32499234 they piss each other off and parted their ways it is getting a litte repetitive...

the original author will not make season 6...i have bad feelings about this...[/q]

Dude, seriously, he just said he was on Series 4 :shake::shake::shake:

Anyway, I was about to add this and the cliffhanger at the end of Series 5 is intriguing indeed.
</comment>
<comment username="Myrdin T Sasnak" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 20:51:55 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 20:51:55 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 20:51:55 +0000" thumbs="2">
Ah, what's 32499234? If it has something to do with something I have not seen in Supernatural, I don't want to know. If it is some geek term then I very mucg want to know. Enlighten me, please!
</comment>
<comment username="evil_puck" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 12:39:46 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 12:39:46 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 12:39:46 +0000" thumbs="2">
forgot the "times"

after season 3 the story between the brothers repeat itself over and over again and becomes really boring... 

hope the 6 season will be like the first 2 (which were supreme...)
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1385527" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="4993" objectname="The Sting Game" username="Myrdin T Sasnak" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 14:24:42 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 14:24:42 +0000" thumbs="3" imageid="16582">
	<body>[b]Leverage[/b]
It would be hard to list a favorite of mine right now between Royal Pains, Burn Notice, and Leverage (why are all the really neat shows now on cable stations?), but I think I'd have to go with Leverage. Great characters and stories.</body>
	
			
		</item>
	<item id="1385534" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="10784" objectname="F*ck This! (Sex, Drugs and Rock &amp; Roll)" username="evil_puck" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 15:12:43 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 15:15:54 +0000" thumbs="4" imageid="44197">
	<body>At the moment waiting for the new and last two pillars of the earth parts... i did not like the book, but the series rocks!

waiting for new stuff from s. moffat. Doctor who and Sherlock (SPLENDIT!)...

Waiting for dexter season 5
Waiting for the incredible and perfect VENTURE BROS ...new episodes...ahh where are they
Waiting for dr house season 6 in german
Maybe beginning to watch Big Bang...
waiting for bones season 5 in german... (watched all so far in german and want to continiue this...)

watching the 329493249 time The Avengers with Emma Peel (my girlfriend and i love it since years and will love it in years to come...british humor is sooo cool)  and sopranos 

also watching old dr. who episodes with tom baker. He is the man

also to watch in next time (HBO rocks..) John adams, generation kills


last watched : pacific... very nice. I like how they show that americans were not really the good guys they always pretent they are. War always sucks...

</body>
	
			<comment username="Wind Lane" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 18:09:57 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 18:09:57 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 18:09:57 +0000" thumbs="2">
New Venture brothers episodes begin next month if I'm not mistaken.
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1385601" objecttype="thing" subtype="rpgitem" objectid="44758" objectname="Farscape Roleplaying Game" username="blark" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 17:25:13 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 17:25:13 +0000" thumbs="5" imageid="531023">
	<body>Been watching [b]Farscape[/b] on the Netflix stream.  I'd always been curious about the show, but had missed far too much of its original run to get into it properly.

We've just finished the first season and are an episode into the second...  I think I like this show better than Star Trek.  I revel in my heresy.</body>
	
			<comment username="Wulf Corbett" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 17:29:52 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 17:29:52 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 17:29:52 +0000" thumbs="2">
Farscape started strange &amp; got weirder. It managed to stay good all the way through some very dodgy ideas, and at it's best - which was often - it was excellent.

But the character swapping episode was... bizarre... :surprise:
</comment>
<comment username="Ugavine" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 12:38:07 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 12:38:07 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 12:38:07 +0000" thumbs="2">

Farscape is a brilliant series.
</comment>
<comment username="DreadFuzzy" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 18:23:31 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 18:23:31 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 18:23:31 +0000" thumbs="2">
My favourite series ever.  Season 1 starts slow (but good) and really kicks off once Chiana joins the crew.  The ride just gets wilder, crazier and more unbelievably amazing with each passing episode.  And when you hit the ending to Season 4 remember that when it was originally broadcast as far as anyone knew [i]that was [b]it![/b][/i].  Peacekeeper Wars didn't come about until sometime later, largely due to sustained fan pressure.  The ending to Season 4 is... well, just spare a thought for those of us who watched it at the time.  Damn.
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1385609" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="37111" objectname="Battlestar Galactica" username="GodfatherPTS" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 17:35:29 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 17:39:14 +0000" thumbs="4" imageid="354500">
	<body>Finishing up Season 3 of [b]Battlestar Galactica[/b] as we speak. First disc of Season 4 arrives today from Netflix. Love Admiral Adama, Chief, Helo. I really hate the Lee Adama/Kara Thrace storyline though. Ugh, what do those two see in each other (what does anyone else see in them for that matter)?

Two days ago I rewatched the entire 1st season of [b]Flight of the Conchords[/b] while I unpacked my moving boxes. Too bad the second season was such a flop. Still laugh out loud every time I hear "If you're in to it".

The show I started watching this summer and LOVED is [b]Bones[/b]. I started with Season 3, which just blew my mind. What a great, and tragic (for the show, i.e. the loss of Zach, maybe the best character on the show), end to the Gorgamon storyline. I am slightly afraid it won't be able to live up to that season, but I still love Bones and Booth. Oh, and Sweets is the greatest (I'd like to be that guy's friend, I think).

Also, just started [b]Weeds[/b] on Netflix. Enjoying it so far.</body>
	
			
		</item>
	<item id="1385653" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="12943" objectname="Go Mental" username="elgin_j" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 20:03:46 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 20:03:46 +0000" thumbs="2" imageid="196452">
	<body>I've just polished Season 2 of [b]The Mentalist[/b] although it has definitely declined since the loss of certain characters.  I'll have to see whether Season 3 is much of anything - needs a lot more Red John methinks.

Also been watching [b]Shogun[/b] miniseries and, as previously mentioned, [b]Supernatural[/b].  

I've also been subjected to [b]The Hills[/b] &amp; [b]The City[/b] courtesy of my gossip-adoring wife and, bizarrely, [b]Legend of the Seeker[/b].  Not a fan of any although the latter started to interest me a little.  Still find it strange that my wife would be interested in a fantasy series at all, let alone more than I but there we go.

Shan't be watching much of anything as of next month, though, when I head off somewhere hot and sandy and full of friendly locals.</body>
	
			<comment username="Liggur" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 23:45:06 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 23:45:06 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 23:45:06 +0000" thumbs="2">
My wife Hates Legend of the Seeker, and refuses to watch it, nothing like the books that she has read.
Ive not read them, so I dont mind it.
</comment>
<comment username="JohnBandettini" date="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 23:47:25 +0000" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 23:47:25 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 23:47:25 +0000" thumbs="4">
But don't you think Brass is a great game.   :p
</comment>
<comment username="elgin_j" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 06:43:47 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 06:43:47 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 06:43:47 +0000" thumbs="1">
[q="JohnBandettini"]But don't you think Brass is a great game.   :p[/q]

Wasn't it you that had a massive sense of humour failure last time I talked about how crap Brass is!?

Brass is shit, by the way :ninja:
</comment>
<comment username="evil_puck" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 13:50:44 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 13:50:44 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 13:50:44 +0000" thumbs="2">
[q="elgin_j"][q="JohnBandettini"]But don't you think Brass is a great game.   :p[/q]

Wasn't it you that had a massive sense of humour failure last time I talked about how crap Brass is!?

Brass is shit, by the way :ninja:[/q]

thank god you are an english man(so you burn in hell:devil:). one moment i thought this act of blasphmy was meant for real^^...
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1385881" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="23656" objectname="Chuck-It Chicken!" username="Liggur" postdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 23:49:15 +0000" editdate="Sat, 28 Aug 2010 23:49:15 +0000" thumbs="4" imageid="152412">
	<body>Watching Season 3 of [b]Chuck[/b]
[b]Legend of the Seeker[/b] season 2
Also [b]Numb3rs[/b] season 4 

And as commented on in an earlier thread, [b]Dexter[/b], season 4 has just started.</body>
	
			<comment username="eugene256" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 04:40:38 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 04:40:38 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 04:40:38 +0000" thumbs="3">
Finally, another Chuck fan!
</comment>
<comment username="elgin_j" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 06:44:55 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 06:44:55 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 06:44:55 +0000" thumbs="0">
Chuck is good but I don't find it compelling viewing.  The 2 Nerd Herd geeks and the awesome theme song are the best things about it.  
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1385899" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="19273" objectname="Curbstone" username="Beaudacious" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 00:28:07 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 00:28:07 +0000" thumbs="6" imageid="88637">
	<body>[b]Make mine Curb Your Enthusiasm![/b]

:laugh:

Doesn't seem like many BG Geeks go for this type of humor.  Oh well.

I have a hold request in at the library for Season 7.</body>
	
			<comment username="remus" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 04:05:08 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 04:05:08 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 04:05:08 +0000" thumbs="3">
Curb is great!
</comment>
<comment username="Folterknecht" date="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 11:28:09 +0000" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 11:28:09 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 11:28:09 +0000" thumbs="3">
I was waiting for this to show up. I probably would have added it myself if you hadn't. There are a lot of interesting and funny shows around, but the humor in Curb is really unique. I watched the first season and just started on the second.

Shows like this and [i]It's Always Sunny In Philadelphia[/i] are a superb alternative for GenY youngsters like me who like the [i]Seinfeld[/i] kind of humor but would rather have it presented in a fresh way that doesn't scream "This was made in the nineties!".
</comment>

		</item>
	<item id="1386043" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="31635" objectname="The Nurses Game" username="remus" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 04:11:50 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 04:11:50 +0000" thumbs="3" imageid="243986">
	<body>I'm watching alot that's already been mentioned

Mad Men
Psych
Pillars of the Earth (just finished)
Weeds
True Blood
Entourage
Louie
U.S. of Tara (finished a while ago, but worth mentioning)

One that hasn't been mentioned yet, that's worth mentioning is Showtime's [b]Nurse Jackie[/b].  

Edie Falco is fantastic as the pill-popping nurse with attitude.  Excellent writing.  Great show.

Looking forward to [b]Dexter [/b]Season 5 and the upcoming season of [b]Always Sunny in Philadelphia[/b]

I'm also looking forward to the new HBO series [b]Boardwalk [/b]from Martin Scorcese starring Steve Buscemi.</body>
	
			
		</item>
	<item id="1386201" objecttype="family" subtype="boardgamefamily" objectid="11" objectname="Mystery Rummy" username="Doug1020" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 11:39:07 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 11:39:07 +0000" thumbs="3" imageid="727398">
	<body>Can't believe no one has posted [b]Mystery Science Theater 3000[/b].  Unfortunately I discovered this gem just a season or two before it was canceled by the SciFi Network.  

We used to riff the bad movies in the back row of the theater at age 10, but professional comedians do it so much better!  A few references may be obscure, some date back to previous shows, but most of the jokes are easily caught.  Don't drink soda (unless you don't mind squirting it out the nostrils).

Since the collection DVDs keep coming, I now collect something besides board games.
</body>
	
			
		</item>
	<item id="1386203" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="4355" objectname="Therapy" username="Likeless" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 11:55:21 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 11:55:21 +0000" thumbs="3" imageid="13822">
	<body>[size=18][COLOR=#FFFFFF][b][BGCOLOR=#FF00CC]Being Erica[/BGCOLOR][/b][/COLOR][/size]

A time travel therapy drama. I'm enjoying it far more than I would have thought given that description.</body>
	
			
		</item>
	<item id="1386312" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="31978" objectname="Hustle" username="JoffW" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 14:08:57 +0000" editdate="Fri, 25 Mar 2011 13:02:14 +0000" thumbs="3" imageid="0">
	<body>Perhaps the best TV series ever made, broadcast on BBC, is Hustle. Seasons 1 and 2 are great, season 3 was not bad, a disappointing season 4 but picked up once more for season 5 and 6. Now awaiting Season 6 to hit DVD.</body>
	
			
		</item>
	<item id="1386472" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="933" objectname="New Orleans Big Band" username="Schandi" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 17:37:34 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 17:37:34 +0000" thumbs="3" imageid="155228">
	<body>After The Wire ended and left me wanting for more shows that realistically portray life I checked out what else David Simon has to offer. So I cam across [b]Treme[/b], a show about New Orleans a couple of months after hurricane Katrina.

Not only does it deliver in terms of "real" characters and plot, its great musical scenes made me enjoy Jazz more and made me want to visit New Orleans one day to join a second line.</body>
	
			
		</item>
	<item id="1386506" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="22511" objectname="Stargate Trading Card Game" username="DreadFuzzy" postdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 18:27:36 +0000" editdate="Sun, 29 Aug 2010 18:27:36 +0000" thumbs="3" imageid="211570">
	<body>Currently my wife and I are (finally) watching [b]Stargate Atlantis[/b] courtesy of LoveFilm.  We've watched all of SG-1 including the movies so it was past time that we watched this.  After we're done (and once LoveFilm get it) we'll probably watch Stargate universe.

We also very recently sat and watched the entirety of [b]The Wire[/b], which was a stunning piece of television

Other than that I'm looking forward to checking out Season 2 of [b]Fringe[/b] and I'm seriously considering breaking out my copies of [b]Firefly[/b] and [b]Farscape[/b] for another run through.</body>
	
			
		</item>
	<item id="1387114" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="24480" objectname="The Pillars of the Earth" username="leadman" postdate="Mon, 30 Aug 2010 05:49:09 +0000" editdate="Mon, 30 Aug 2010 05:49:09 +0000" thumbs="3" imageid="212815">
	<body>I read Ken Follett's book and found it fascinating, couldn't stop reading it. The 8-part mini series isn't bad either although they had to make sacrifices to cram 1000 book pages into 8 hours of TV show.</body>
	
			
		</item>
	<item id="1387235" objecttype="thing" subtype="boardgame" objectid="9796" objectname="VEX Flag Card Game" username="Ugavine" postdate="Mon, 30 Aug 2010 11:16:45 +0000" editdate="Mon, 30 Aug 2010 11:16:45 +0000" thumbs="3" imageid="84421">
	<body>Vexed

It's a new comedy/detective show on BBC 2, Sunday nights in the UK.  While I'm not into detective shows at all I am actually enjoying this.  And it's not a slapstick comedy, more of a dry humour, mostly about the character Jack being a jerk.</body>
	
			
		</item>
</geeklist>